Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5728
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VIII: Office Files, 1979
  - Railroads: Railroad Ownership, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Railroads: Auto Train Corporation, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Press releases in re possible merger between the Chessie System and Seaboard Air Lines.
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Newsletters and revenue statistics.
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: Hospital Association (General), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations AFL-CIO (General), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Legislative Council, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous Organizations (General), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Includes pamphlets on home and workplace safety.
  - Other Organizations: Transportation Research Forum, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau of the Middle West (Gus Homer), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    Correspondence and filings in re the ICC's proposed plan to revise employee classifications in the railroad industry.
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Includes financial reports and studies on the value and use of the LABOR building's parking lot in downtown Washington DC.
  - Other Organizations: Special Election Year Editions of LABOR Newspaper, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: City of Hope, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - International Affairs: General, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    Includes ITF newsletters.
  - International Affairs: Bureau of International Labor Affairs (Foreign Visitors), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Commuter Problems: General, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Series IX: Desk Files, 1975
  - Desk File, January-March 1975 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    Outgoing correspondence files of the executives of RLEA.
  - Desk File, April-June 1975 [folder 1 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 28a)
  - Desk File, April-June 1975 [folder 2 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 28b)
  - Desk File, April-June 1975 [folder 3 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 28c)
  - Desk File, July-September 1975 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 40, Folder 29a)
  - Desk File, July-September 1975 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 40, Folder 29b)
- Series X: Office Files, 1980
  - Government: Executive Branch, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Government: House and Senate, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Government: Government Agencies (General), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Includes annual report from the U.S. Metric Board.
  - Government: United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Government: Department of Transportation, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Government: Department of Transportation - Staff Appointments, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Government: Transportation Association of America (Harriman Awards), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 41, Folder 8a)
    Includes press release and circulars.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 41, Folder 8b)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration - Alcoholism, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Government: Department of Transportation - "Railroad Management and Engineering: Educational Needs and Recommended Programs", 1980 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    March 1980, Final report. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Special Investigation Report - Tank Car Structural Integrity After Derailment, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Derailment of Western Pacific Railroad Company Freight Train UP 3734 West, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    April 9, 1980. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Reports - Brief Format, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident report - Head-on Collision Between AMTRAK Train 82 and Seaboard Coast Line Extra 2771 South, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    April 2, 1980. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Head-on Collision of Baltimore and Ohio Freight Trains Extra 6474 East and Extra 4367 West, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    February 12, 1980. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Derailment of AMTRAK Train 7, The Empire Builder, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    March 14, 1980. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Head-End Collision of Nine Burlington Northern Locomotive Units with a Standing Freight Train, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    February 16, 1980. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Reports - Brief Format, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Derailment of AMTRAK Train 4, the Southwest Limited, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    October 2, 1979. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Rear-End Collision of CONRAIL Commuter Trains, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    October 16, 1979. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Head-End Collision of AMTRAK Train 392 and Illinois Central gulf Train 51, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    October 12, 1979. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Reports - Brief Format, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board - Safety Effectiveness Evaluation of the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration's Rulemaking Process, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Rear End Collision of Southern Pacific Transportation Company Freight Trains, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    July 24, 1979. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Rear End Collision of Consolidated Rail Corporation Freight Trains, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    October 1, 1979. Bound volume.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Special Investigation Report - The Accident Performance of Tank Car Safeguards, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board Railroad Accident Report - Derailment of Union Pacific Railroad Freight Train, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    July 31, 1979. Bound volume.
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration - Staff Appointments, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Government: Office of Railroad Safety - Safety Inspectors, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration-Department of Transportation - Safety - Rules, Regulations, Petitions, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Government: Safety Appliance Acts, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Government: Highway Grade Crossing Matters, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Government: Power Brakes, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Government: Locomotive Inspection, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Government: Signal Rules, Standards, and Instructions (RS and I Cases), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Government: Approval of Changes in Signal Installations (BS-AP Cases), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Government: Hours of Service, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Government: Track Maintenance and Inspection Standards, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration-Department of Transportation - Accidents, Incidents, Reports, Classifications and Investigations, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 39a)
    Includes bound accident investigation reports.
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration-Department of Transportation - Accidents, Incidents, Reports, Classifications and Investigations [Folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 41, Folder 39b)
  - Government: Labor Department (General), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Government: Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) [Folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 41, Folder 42a)
  - Government: Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) [Folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 41, Folder 42b)
  - Government: Urban Mass Transportation Administration Section 13(c) (General), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Rail Services Planning Office (General), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    ICC Newsletters
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Membership and Staff Appointments, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission - Statistics, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    Letter announcing the discontinuance of "Transport Economics,"
  - Government: Bureau of Transport Economics and Statistics (General), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 274 Sub 1 - Special Procedures for Proposed Railroad Abandonments, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 282 Sub 2 and 3 - Railroad Consolidation Procedures, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 274 Sub 2 - Proposed Rulemaking, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 270 Sub 2 - Railroad Freight Service Investigation, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte 361 - Exemption from Section 5(2) of the Interstate Commerce Commission Act, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Government: National Mediation Board (General), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 54)
    Includes a notice announcing a proposal to reduce the membership of the NRAB.
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Emergency Board Reports, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Membership and Staff Appointments, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board (General), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Government: Special Board of Adjustment 605, Regarding 2/7/65 Agreement - Awards, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Government: Arbitration Board, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board - First Division, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board Second Division, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board Third Division, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board Fourth Division, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board - Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board - Membership, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Quarterly Review, December 1980. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Quarterly Review, August 1980. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Quarterly Review, August 1980. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Quarterly Review, April 1980 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Tax Tables, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board (General), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Reports for Railway Labor Executives Association Meetings, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Includes financial statements and actuarial reports.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board Membership and Staff Appointments, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Administrative Practices and Procedures, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Circulars
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Field Offices - Schedule of Regular Itinerant Service, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Status of Funds, Actuarial Reports (Monthly Benefit Statistics), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    Monthly benefit statements
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Retirement, Benefits, and Unemployment Insurance Systems, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    Includes a confidential letter from C.J. Chamberlain with an actuarial report predicting an imminent cash shortfall. Also includes circulars for the chief executives of railway labor organizations.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Statistical Supplement for 1979 Annual Report, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Educational Programs, Meetings, Films, Etcetera (Scheduled Informational Conferences), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Supplemental Retirement Plans (Supplemental Pensions), Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board National Reporting Officers Memoranda, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Administration of Medicare, Financial Intermediary, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Government: President's Committee on the Handicapped, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    Includes newsletters and a pamphlet, "Specifications for making buildings and facilities accessible to and usable by physically handicapped people."
  - Government: National Railroad Passenger Corporation (AMTRAK), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    Includes map of national routes and a report of suggested improvements for the system.
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Government: Railway Labor Executives Association - Labor Subcommittee 880 (James E. Burke, Chairman) [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 42, Folder 27a)
    Includes minutes of meetings, agendas, and filings in front of SBA 880.
  - Government: Railway Labor Executives Association - Labor Subcommittee 880 (James E. Burke, Chairman) [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 42, Folder 27b)
  - Government: Consolidated Rail Corporation (CONRAIL), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    Includes circulars in re lawsuit brought against Conrail by RLLEA for federal safety violations.
  - Government: United States Railway Association - Federal Funding of CONRAIL, December 1980. (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Government: New England Rail Restructuring Analysis, 31 March 1980. (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Government: New England Rail Restructuring Analysis - Task V, Labor Practices Analysis, April 1980 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Government: National Transportation Policy Study Commission, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Government: Department of Energy (General), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Judicial: Court Cases (General) [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 42, Folder 34a)
    Includes correspondence and filings for the cases in folders 35-40, below.
  - Judicial: Court Cases (General) [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 42, Folder 34b)
  - Judicial: Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul and Pacific Railroad Company versus Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    July 1980. Bound volume.
  - Judicial: Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Company versus Railway Labor Executives Association, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    May 19, 1980. Bound volume.
  - Judicial: Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad Company versus Railway Labor Executives Association, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Judicial: United Transportation Union versus Long Island Railroad Company and Metropolitan Transportation Authority of New York, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Judicial: Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company versus United States of America and the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    Also Railway Labor Executives Association versus United States of America and the Interstate Commerce Commission. July 28, 1980. Bound.
  - Judicial: Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Company versus Railway Labor Executives Association, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    May 19, 1980.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads, Railroad Labor/Management Relations, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Includes letter from FRA Administrator John Sullivan in re RLEA's decision to reinstate the Labor-Management Committee and Santa Fe Railroad pamphlets.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Labor Management Task Force on Terminals, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railroad Labor Management Relations, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Immigration Problems, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Employee Assistance Program Workshop (Alcoholism), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - railway Labor Executives Association: Federal Railroad Administration-Department of Transportation - Alcoholism, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Bound volume, " Prevalence, Costs, and Handling of Drinking Problems on Seven Railroads."
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Subcommittee on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Correspondence in re RLEA EAP Workshop. Also includes report on Amtrak's EAP.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Includes copy of Supreme Court's decision reversing lower court's award to benefits to railroad retirees. Also includes correspondence with legislators in re amendments to Railroad Retirement Act.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on National Transportation Policy, Mergers, Consolidations, and Passenger Service, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Legislative Representatives, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Director Governmental Affairs Legislative Report, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    Monthly reports from Donald Beattie.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Passes, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Prospective Employees (General), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial Statements, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Insurance Company, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers (General), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Lawyers Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 43, Folder 18a)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Lawyers Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 43, Folder 18b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Strikes (General), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Press Releases, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Railroads: General, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Railroads: Railroad Ownership, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Railroads: Auto Train Corporation, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 43, Folder 24a)
    Newsletters and revenue reports.
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 43, Folder 24b)
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations (General), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Other Organizations: Legislative Council, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: Executive Council, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous Organizations (General), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: Transportation Research Forum, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau of the Middle West ("Gus" Homer), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Other Organizations: Retaining of Labor Bureau of Middle West to Oppose Revision of ICC Reports, Forms A, B, and M-300, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Other Organizations: Special Election Year Editions of LABOR Newspaper, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - International Affairs: General, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    Includes correspondence in re the Iran Hostage Crisis and labor's response to it.
  - International Affairs: Bureau of International Labor Affairs (Foreign Visitors), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Commuter Problems: General, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: General, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Includes list of RLEA endorsements for 1980 elections.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Constitution and By-Laws, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Includes copy of revised By-Laws.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Insurance Company (Employee Certification), 1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Officers and Members, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Railway Supervisors Association, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Includes letter announcing merger of ARSA and BRAC.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Train Dispatchers Association, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Includes letter announcing BRC's disaffiliation from the Railway Employees' Department, AFL-CIO.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Includes letter announcing that due to the dissolution of the Railway Employees' Department, AFL-CIO, all bargaining will be done through the IBEW.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Includes letter announcing that as of October 1, 1980, all bargaining will be done through the IBFO
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association (Joint Maritime Congress), 1980 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 15)